# Pedro Carmo

# Résumé

#### Introduction

Hello, my name is Pedro Carmo. I'm a product designer based in Brooklyn, NY. I recently joined the design team at Kickstarter, working on the Backing feature team and Design Systems team. My focus is improving how our backers interact with and back a project checkout page and helping build and define our component library.

On the side, I mentor Design 101 and Interaction Design students at Designlab.

#### **Skills**

Design, primarily focused on product thinking, interaction design, visual design, user experience and product research. Development, effecient in Html, Css & Scss architecture, Git SCM, Framer.js and working in Rails-dev environments.

### References

Mig Reyes, Design Lead at Trunk Club contact@migreyes.com

Deepa Subramaniam, VP of Product & Design Kickstarter deepa@kickstarter.com

Jason James, *Product Design Lead at Thumbtack* hello@jasonjam.es

## **Experience**

Kickstarter, Product Designer

January 2017—Present

**Teespring**, Product Designer *August 2014—November 2016* 

**DevMynd Software**, Product Designer *November 2013—August 2014* 

Codal Inc., Designer & FE Engineer

March 2013—November 2013

Codal Inc., Design Intern

January 2013—March 2013

**Futura IO**, Design Intern

November 2013—August 2014

#### **Education**

**The Starter League**, Visual Design Student Winter 2012 class

The Starter League, Advanced FE Development Student Spring 2013 class

### **Certifications**

Scrum Product Owner, CSPO Spring 2017